动涤图表在图库窗口中,双击打开Pretest Files文件夹。
找到D,FindTuning中的D。
Enhancing the quality of a garment.
website, and it's not a question.
In the document, Jase, enhancing the quality of the quality of clothing, the texture of the
금 and the quality of the simulation must be adjusted.
Use the function of increasing clothing quality to edit their value.
Select the tool with the term supply of clothing quality.
A window that can adjust the isosceles model simulation attribute value appears.
Click Cancel.
Select the fifth one of the 3D vertical tool bar.
Click the grid.
A grid will appear on the 3D costume.
The particle diameter is the distance between the dots between the grid and the 3D costume.
Reduce the value of the particle diameter in the attribute editor, simulation attribute, and particle diameter.
The smaller the value of the particle diameter, the more grid.
The more realistic the costume shape is, the slower the calculation will be.
Generally, it is operated at the last step.
Select the fifth one of the 3D vertical tool bar.
Click the grid.
The 3D costume will be switched to the normal surface.
Select all the panels at the 2D window.
In the attribute editor, reduce the particle diameter to 5.
Activate simulation.
The 3D costume will be more realistic.
Reduce the value of the particle diameter.
Activate simulation.
In the second 3D window, select the image from the selected panel.
In this way, the 3D costume will be more realistic.
Activate simulation.
The third 3D model will be more realistic.
In the 2D window, select the second 3D model.
In the attribute editor, the model attribute, increase thickness, conflict, here is the conflict thickness.
Conflict thickness refers to the safe distance between the panels.
It is set to prevent collision between the panels, but there is no distance between the real clothing panel and the panel.
So when you want to improve the quality of clothing, you need to reduce the conflict thickness to make 3D clothing more realistic.
You can see that the
combination of the two layers of clothing is good.
In the 2D window, click on all panels.
In the attribute editor,
Adjust the contrast thickness to 1
and activate the simulation
to set it to 3D clothing
Click on the surface of the virtual model at the 3D window
On the surface of the virtual model
The surface distance is 0 to 100
This is the surface diameter of the virtual model
This distance is to prevent the 3D clothing from colliding with the model
But the real person does not have this distance
So when increasing the quality
Reduce the surface diameter to 0
and activate the simulation
Activate the simulation to set the application to 3D clothing
In the simulation tool bar on the 3D tool bar, click on the left-hand side
There is a fast GPU simulation in the output menu bar
Normal speed default
Try the material attribute calculation
These three modes are from top to bottom
The simulation is getting more and more precise
But the simulation speed is getting slower
In general, you can use normal speed
It can accurately simulate the material attribute at a relatively fast speed
Fast GPU simulation speed is the fastest
But the simulation quality is the lowest
Usually used to simulate large pieces of fabric
Such as curtains and so on
Try the material attribute calculation of the material attribute calculation
The simulation speed is the slowest
But the simulation quality is the highest
Can accurately simulate the material attribute
Make the clothing look more real
Usually used in the use of the material measurement
And need to use it in comparison with 3D clothing and practical application
In the 3D tool bar, choose to improve clothing quality tools
Here you can reduce the number of particle
Adjust the model attribute